=The Shoufu Can Read Mind=
= الشوفو يستطيع قراءة العقل =
=Episode 13=
= الحلقة 13 =
Dear,
عزيزي،
we're a family, right?
نحن عائلة ، صحيح؟
Family should help each other, right?
الأسرة يجب أن تساعد بعضها البعض ، أليس كذلك؟
Aren't we soulmates?
ألسنا رفقاء الروح؟
How come we're a family now?
لماذا نحن عائلة الآن؟
If you're not screaming,
إذا كنت لا تصرخ ،
I don't mind
أنا لا أمانع
getting you...
الوصول اليك...
Stop it!
توقف عن ذلك!
(Bad guy.)
(شاب سيء.)
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Why did you fight?
لماذا قاتلت
She said you dislike me
قالت أنك لا تحبني
and you have a mistress out there.
ولديك عشيقة هناك.
She even beat Dan Zhu.
حتى أنها تغلبت على دان تشو.
That's why I was angry
لهذا كنت غاضبًا
and I beat her up.
وضربتها.
Look!
ينظر!
Dan Zhu's face was injured by her.
أصيب وجه دان تشو بسببها.
What? What I said is the truth.
ماذا؟  ما قلته هو الحقيقة.
Just because you're close to Grand Secretariat
فقط لأنك قريب من الأمانة العامة
and General Shen,
والجنرال شين ،
you're bullying others.
أنت تتنمر على الآخرين.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
How dare you gossip about the officers of the imperial court?
كيف تجرؤ على الثرثرة عن ضباط البلاط الإمبراطوري؟
Are you seeking death upon yourself?
هل تطلب الموت على نفسك؟
You...
أنت...
You believe what she said?
هل تصدق ما قالته؟
I trust my wife,
أنا أثق في زوجتي ،
not an outsider.
ليس دخيلا.
Just wait and see!
فقط انتظر وانظر!
My good daughter.
ابنتي الطيبة.
You
أنت
have gone too easy on her.
سهلت عليها.
Father.
أب.
You're indeed my sister.
أنت بالفعل أختي.
You've never lost in a fight
لم تخسر أبدًا في قتال
just like me.
فقط مثلي.
Yanqing,
يانكينغ ،
thanks to you
شكرا لك
that not only we're not in any trouble,
ليس فقط أننا لسنا في مشكلة ،
His Majesty even
جلالة الملك حتى
allows Le
يسمح لو
to study in the Imperial Academy.
للدراسة في الأكاديمية الإمبراطورية.
This is all your contribution.
هذا هو كل مساهمتك.
Father,
أب،
don't forget that
لا تنسى ذلك
he has cheated
لقد غش
your 1,000 taels of gold.
1000 تايل من الذهب.
Let's not
دعنا لا
talk about that.
نتحدث عن ذلك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's go home.
لنذهب إلى المنزل.
(Zheng Dumpling Restaurant)
(مطعم زهينج الدمبلينغ)
The imperial examination case has come to an end.
انتهت قضية الفحص الإمبراطوري.
Tonight,
الليلة،
you'll be moving back to your room, right?
ستعود إلى غرفتك ، أليس كذلك؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Does it hurt?
هل تؤلم؟
If you don't want any scars,
إذا كنت لا تريد أي ندوب ،
don't move.
لا تتحرك.
I thought you're good at fighting.
اعتقدت أنك جيد في القتال.
Yet you've injured yourself.
ومع ذلك فقد جرحت نفسك.
Look at how bad she's injured.
انظر إلى مدى إصابتها.
Am I not good at fighting?
ألست جيد في القتال؟
You're Xu Yanqing's wife.
أنت زوجة شو يانكينغ.
If you face anything
إذا واجهت أي شيء
and you can't protect yourself,
ولا يمكنك حماية نفسك ،
take a step back
خذ خطوة للوراء
and come back to look for me.
وتعود للبحث عني.
(Is he)
(هل هو)
(showing concerns?)
(إظهار المخاوف؟)
(No way.)
(مستحيل.)
(He's just worried that)
(إنه قلق فقط من ذلك)
(I'd be a disgrace to the Grand Secretariat.)
(سأكون وصمة عار على الأمانة العامة.)
(Such an obstinate woman.)
(هذه امرأة عنيدة).
So hungry.
جائع جدا.
As a food blogger,
بصفتك مدونًا للطعام ،
ever since I've come to this place,
منذ أن جئت إلى هذا المكان ،
I haven't eaten any delicacies.
أنا لم أتناول أي طعام شهي.
I want to eat a bowl of hot beef noodles.
أريد أن آكل وعاء من نودلز اللحم البقري الساخن.
I'm hungry as well.
أنا جائع أيضًا.
Dear,
عزيزي،
will you cook for me?
هل تطبخ لي؟